It has begun! Applaud that channel!
Today's guest is this gentleman!
What, what, early! What, too soon!
What? They call us in two seconds.
It's Summer Ando from Memple Superluxe!
You've really come this far!
Watch out!
Hello.
I'm Ando from Memple Ultra Premium.
What are you doing here?
It's so hot!
I heard we're going to have some fun today.
I heard you were going to do something fun.
That's right.
With Natsu like this...
What do you mean, like this?
There's no way I'm going to do a project with Natsu like this.
I thought...
But there is something.
That's why you're dressed like this.
Let's go touring with Mr. Natsu and have a taco party!
It'll be fun!
He's a motorcyclist, so...
I bought that bike too.
I bought the bike because I admired the way Natsu-san rode his Harley.
You're lying!
That's definitely not true!
But it's really cool, so I think it's okay if I put my crotch through it.
You don't say "crotch it"?
What do you call it?
Why don't you just call it "crotch riding" or "tandem"?
I was thinking of riding.
I don't have a license. No! Then I have no choice but to ride again, and again, and again.
I have no choice but to go through the tandem today.
I want to ride on Hinatsu-san's cool Harley, the Fat Boy.
Sure.
Do you want to ride it?
Oh my God, it's so cool!
Here it is.
Is this your favorite? Sure, why did you choose this one? This video is about American people with cool motorcycles, you hear me? Seriously, I was just explaining it to you.
Did you hear me?
No, I didn't.
But that's okay, because you're listening.
I did it once.
I went through it again in private.
You did it again.
Oh, by the way...
It was too dark, so they gave me a ride home.
People probably don't know about our private relationship.
They don't know about our private relationship.
Please explain.
We're drinking buddies.
When I was going through a rough patch.
I lost my house.
He was really great.
He called me out in the pouring rain while I was crying.
What? I didn't know the timing.
He didn't know the timing, but he'd always call me when he knew I was hurt.
When I'm having a hard time, he invites me to a takoyaki party.
It wasn't like a party.
To a takoyaki shop.
It's not a takoyaki shop.
I'm just a takoyaki eater.
You came to eat.
It's like picking up abandoned cats.
He's the kind of person who attracts me.
When I happened to be thinking of stabbing her, I called her.
I'd call her when I was thinking of stabbing her, and she'd cry.
What do you mean? I'm like, "Are you okay? Like, "Are you okay?
Yeah, it's like a God thing.
It's all in the timing, isn't it?
The takoyaki I had at that time was unforgettably delicious.
I'm so glad.
I couldn't use my hand because of the broken bone.
You did your best to eat with the hand you could use.
Yes, I ate with my left hand the whole time.
But I ate about 30 pieces.
They were so good, I ate them all, even though I don't eat that much.
I was so happy because I was eating so much.
And I didn't eat any rice then either.
I'll take you to the takoyaki today to get that takoyaki. With whom?
With whom?
Really?
No, sir.
It's always the guests.
Let the guests do the talking.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry I'm so unreliable.
No, no, no.
No, no, no. I had something in mind.
I'm so glad.
I'm glad you did.
So, are we gonna go now?
Let's go.
Okay, let's get to it.
Okay? I'm in.
I'm in.
Wow, you look great.
That's so cool.
Yeah!
It's cool.
Don't get in.
Okay, I'm just going to put it through again.
What do you mean, let me ride in the back?
I've never ridden in the back.
Can I put my feet up here?
Put them on.
Squeeze.
Not dangerous.
You know what?
It's not a bike, it's not dangerous
My glasses just fogged up.
Fingerprints are amazing
My fingerprints are all over the place.
What do you want me to do? Here?
Uh, where?
Do you want to squeeze it?
Here?
Is it easier?
Yeah, it's okay.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You sure? I'm worried.
You ready?
Yeah, I'm coming, okay?
Oh, you're leaving? What, you're not going? Are you going? Yeah, we're going? Are you going?
You're not going?
Yeah, I'm going. I'm off.
Bye-bye.
I'm leaving Teletext.
I'm leaving.
I'm sorry if I fall off.
No, I can't. I can't. I can't.
I hope they catch him!
It's so cold!
It's cold.
But I like this bike for style.
It's nice, isn't it?
It feels good to ride a bike, doesn't it?
You're smoking hard.
I'm working on it. I'm working on it. I'm working on it.
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine.
I want to go touring.
Don't you want to go deep into the mountains?
I'd get lost deep in the mountains.
Or go glamping?
Glamping? Like camping?
You can go glamping and leave your stuff behind.
Where you can go as a couple and do, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh...
Where you can do porn? No, you can do it anywhere.
Can we do it already? You can do it anywhere, right?
You don't go out with them, do you? I'm too busy right now.
I don't do it at all. I don't really go glamping or camping or anything like that.
You don't like going out?
No. I don't go out to eat or drink at all.
That's why I saw Natsu so much at a certain restaurant when I used to go there.
I also saw her at a cab stand at Nakano Station.
During the typhoon, Natsu was standing in line at the cab stand soaking wet.
What was she doing?
It was a long time ago, like 4 years ago.
That's a long time ago.
You like Nakano, don't you?
I love Nakano.
I used to go to Nakano Broadway all the time.
Nakano Broadway?
Where do you go? Taco Chef?
No, Nakano Ropeway... the grocery store.
I used to go there.
I used to go to the women's wear section in the basement.
I used to buy pajamas there.
You go to the women's wear department?
Yes, I used to buy pajamas in the shopping arcade in Nakano.
Wow.
Let's have a drink at Koenji.
Do you go to Koenji often?
Yes, often.
Lately, I've been trying to find a drink I like.
It's a pai chu. White sake.
It's written "white liquor" and called "pai chu".
Pai chu.
Doesn't it smell bad when you drink it?
No, it's terrible.
It smells like alcohol. Like shochu.
I don't drink soju.
What's that? What's tequila, not Aomori?
Tequila soda, and some Chinese stuff... and why is that... that's Pai Chua... that's Pai Chua... and I smelled it and said I haven't been playing at all... and I wanted to have some fun...
I can't afford to play with someone I don't know well
I have to be with someone I know well, or I won't do it.
Not someone I can talk to like this... or someone I can talk to properly.
Jingu?
Jingu.
Wow, that feels good!
Yay!
Nakagawa.
Is this Jingu Stadium?
Heh.
Do you usually ride a motorcycle?
I definitely ride my bike when I'm on the radio.
Heh.
Looks like it's easy to ride.
Yeah, it's better when there are fewer cars.
I used to ride all the time at night when I had a moped.
It's nice. Look at this. The autumn leaves.
It's amazing. What kind of tree is it? It's a ginkgo.
Do you like ginkgo?
I don't like it.
Dislike it? Like it? Taste ginkgo? Hate it, hate it, hate it...
Like it?
You don't like gingko nuts?
No, I don't like gingko nuts.
Not good?
I'm a little-known fact...
It's a discoloration.
I can tell.
That's why I don't have ginkgo nuts.
Chinese food is fine.
Dumplings...
I love dumplings.
Soup, Chinese soup.
It's delicious, isn't it?
You can't eat it, can you, Onatsu?
I couldn't eat the steamed egg custard.
Oh, there's a lot of silver in it.
I used to like it, but I couldn't eat it after I ate too much and puked.
But it's hard to tell. I couldn't eat it after it was the same color as chawanmushi and vomit, but it's kind of hard to tell, isn't it?
It's the same color as steamed egg custard and vomit.
No, no, no, no, the color depends on what you've already eaten.
You haven't had chawanmushi since then?
But recently, this year...
I made a bowl of chawanmushi.
It's delicious. I can eat it now.
I'm over it.
You don't have to conquer it.
On the contrary.
It's easy to pinpoint what you can eat.
So it's easy to choose.
The menu.
You don't get lost?
No, not at all.
Where are you going?
Is this the Shinagawa side?
I had a drive, but... boo-boo... is that the Shinagawa way?
I had a drive, but I did it with a beginner and a guy who's just starting out on a bike.
It's very nice. You are open? In everyday life.
I'm always open.
All the time?
But isn't it usually like this?
When I see you, I'm like this.
I mean, the tension is like this all the time.
It's always been like this.
There's no "way" or "way" or something like that, but on the other hand, there's nothing really dark either.
Yes, it's like this all the time.
But when Natsu-san gets drunk, he might get a little flustered.
I was listening to Natsu-san's love story so nonchalantly.
Sorry.
Oh, I see.
Oh no!
That's so badass!
That's amazing!
That feels good!
It feels good!
Oh, man!
Is it the ocean?
Have you ever had a boyfriend or something ride in the back?
I have, with a boyfriend.
Do you like to let him ride in the back?
I prefer to drive myself instead of riding in the back.
It's cool.
Do you and your boyfriend talk when you're riding together?
We do.
What do you talk about?
Like, "I love you.
It's hard to concentrate.
But we make small talk.
Like, "That feels good.
I don't say I like you.
I don't say I like you when I'm driving.
Look, right.
Wow! The ocean!
That's the Rainbow Bridge.
Oh, wow. But you know, it would be cool to ride a bike on the Rainbow Bridge.
I think it would be cool to ride a bike around the Rainbow Bridge.
Scene near the Rainbow Bridge.
Are you okay? Come a little closer.
Who do you know well?
I don't know anyone I'm close to.
Oh, really?
Who do you usually hang out with?
Honda and Tsubasa Honda.
What do you do with Tsubasa?
What do you do with Honda and Tsubasa Tsubasa?
Tsubasa-chan usually goes to Tsubasa's house.
I usually call Tsubasa "Bike-chan".
So when we talk...
Do you like motorcycles?
I don't know. Probably not.
Why not?
Tsubasa's YouTube channel calls them Honda bikes.
Oh, yeah.
That's why I call her Bike-chan.
I see.
What do you and Tsubasa do at home?
He serves me dinner.
He cooks for me.
Cooking, casseroles, stuff like that.
Oh, that's great. He cooks a lot of water, a lot of water, and the best part is, he cooks takoyaki.
I'm so happy! I usually do a lot of cooking at home.
Summer likes to eat the food that the gashi like to eat. Gaki? Gaki likes omu-rice and beef bowl.
Oh, I love it!
You've got that under control too?
Yes, omelettes... I want to be the best at it.
Cut the omelet like this.
I want to cut the omelette like this and make it semi-cooked inside like this.
Oh, that beautiful thing.
Yes, yes, yes, I want to learn how to do that.
It would be cool if I could do that.
It would be cool. It would be nice.
I make omu-rice too.
What?
Even though I don't eat it.
So when my dad comes to Tokyo sometimes, I tell him to take me out to eat.
Who's telling who? Who tells my dad to eat?
I tell him to eat his dinner.
I think it's the other way around.
I make him omu-rice.
That's sweet.
I'm sure he'd like that.
He eats it in an instant.
That's scary.
It only takes a second.
It's not that I'm scared, it's just that you're happy.
My daughter made you an omelet with rice.
I'm already impressed.
And the ketchup on the omu-rice...
I'll write it down and serve it.
What do you say to that, Dad?
Look at it.
He says it's delicious.
It's okay.
He doesn't say anything.
That's sweet of you, Dad.
He doesn't even know I'm here.
Dad, I haven't seen you in a while.
For how long?
I don't know.
When I was chosen for the red carpet.
Congratulations. Thank you.
But I never heard from my dad or anyone else.
Oh, I see.
No one wants you here.
What? Is that so?
Ha-ha-ha.
Suddenly? Suddenly you're in it.
Why?
What's the matter?
You're in it all of a sudden?
It's not going to make anyone happy.
Mmm-hmm.
What's the matter?
You're soaking wet all of a sudden.
Mmm-hmm.
But... it's so much love!
I'm so glad we went through this again.
It feels so good!
The air and the heart... so nice... so nice.
Is this the Gate Bridge? Which one? This one?
That's not it.
That one? It's just up ahead.
The Gate Bridge.
There's a lot of motorcyclists here.
It's beautiful.
Yeah, well, my dad's a motorcyclist.
Really?
It's like a big...
But it's a big one.
Yeah, we're the same.
Not a Harley, but a big one,
And he comes to Tokyo on a motorcycle.
Wow.
He really likes motorcycles.
He loves motorcycles.
He spends a lot of time on his bike.
Amazing.
What does your father do?
He used to be a fund manager.
You and your son are like that. Wow, look at you.
It's so beautiful. Look.
Oh, my God, you're so beautiful! Oh, my God!
Evening?
Look at this!
Oh, my God!
I didn't know you could get such a great view in Tokyo!
Yeah!
It's beautiful!
You can see it with the naked eye on a motorcycle! It's beautiful!
I love that you can see it with the naked eye on a bike! It feels so live!
You get a direct view of the scenery!
I think I had something to drink... It's so beautiful!
There's Mt. Fuji on the right!
I can see it, I can see it, I can see it, I can see it!
I see it, I see it!
Wow, is that it?
Mt. Fuji.
Wow, it's Mt. Fuji.
This? Fuji is from Yamanashi, right?
Like Yamanashi. That's amazing.
Is it amazing that you know it's in Yamanashi?
I thought it was amazing.
It's so beautiful.
The sky is so nice.
It's really nice. This is a great picture right now.
Wow, it's beautiful!
It feels so good!
It's so strange that it's in the back of a building like this.
Hey!
It's a very strange mix of feelings, and it's very moving.
I'm glad I got to show it to you!
I'm glad I was able to show it to you.
I'm glad I got to show it to you.
What was that tea doing in school?
In school?
I didn't hang out at school.
I didn't have any friends.
Not much.
So I just stayed at home and watched TV.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That sounds like fun.
What do you watch? I don't know.
I used to watch comedy shows.
I was a TV kid.
That's right.
I watched everything.
Natsu, what made you decide to start comedy?
I like comedy shows myself.
When you were in school?
Yeah, middle school.
That's when you decided to become a comedian?
Yes, in there.
There was a woman named Unlucky Goto.
She was a pin comedian.
She was yelling that her partner ran away from her.
It was a kinneta.
I felt sorry for her.
And then she came out with a flip
I thought, "Oh, I'm going to be his partner.
I thought, "Oh, I'll be his partner," and I sent him a letter,
I sent him a letter, and he sent me back a letter saying that he would be my partner.
I got a letter back saying that I would be his partner. He replied that he would quit comedy when he went to college, and that he was very grateful for the offer, but that he was sorry.
He was very polite. He is a very nice person. He is a very nice person.
And then he turned me down.
I think it was around the third grade of junior high school or junior high school that I started to think to myself, "I love comedy.
I love comedy!
I became a freshman in high school, and I was working as a staff member of the band.
And the drummer of the band,
The drummer of the band told me that one of his classmates was in comedy and he would introduce me to him,
So the two guys formed a trio, with me joining the duo.
Wow, you were a trio at first.
First trio.
So, while doing various things in high school, I was working as a staff member of a band.
I'm too busy with my backstage work.
No, no, I didn't think about making a living at all, I just wanted to do what I wanted to do. Yu-chan, I'm glad you're doing what you really love.
That's true.
That's great. That's why you've made it to the M-1 and so on, isn't it?
I'm grateful for that, because M-1 is really great.
But how long have you been doing music?
I started working as an idol around 2013.
Yes, that's right.
But when I say "music," I don't mean that I've been a solo artist for 3 or 4 years.
I started my solo career about 3 or 4 years ago.
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
Finally Kohaku.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I mean, isn't it amazingly early?
You don't call it "pin" or "solo"?
Kohaku is amazing, to be in it.
I never thought I'd be in it, it wasn't even a goal of mine.
I'm not just thankful, I'm really surprised.
It is a surprise, isn't it?
It's like, "Oh, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no. You work really hard, you know.
She makes her own music, too, which is amazing.
I sometimes cook rice while listening to his music.
I've never been under the Rainbow Bridge.
I'm not impressed with Zaaste Secondly, I don't think I'll be able to play for another 4 years...
I've been working on the second since '15. I see. Yes, yes, yes. If you could get out, would you want to?
I'd like to do comedy when I get settled.
Do you like comic storytelling?
I like comedy. It's fun.
You don't do comedy?
No, I don't. I can't do that.
Comedy.
Comedy is the hardest job.
Isn't it hard to make music, too?
Music is lonely, or hard, or lonely. It's very lonely.
Don't you get a "wow" feeling when you're making something?
I feel mentally down. When I'm making music.
I stay in my room all the time. I wonder if it's the same for you, too.
I envy your partner.
Oh, that's true. He must be very reassuring. Is that so? I envy your partner.
He must be very reassuring.
I can only rely on him because he's like that.
Isn't he so good? Mr. Kazurator, having a partner is so nice.
I'm so grateful.
He's so cool! I lost the keys to Okun's house and he won't come in.
A week ago, I lost my keys to my house, and in the middle of the night
5 am, 5 am?
I lost my keys at the end of an all-nighter.
I couldn't get in the house.
I didn't know what to do at that time.
I should have just gone to Natsu's house then.
Eh, tell me!
But I thought she might be a little busy, or asleep, or something.
But tell her?
I told her, and she stopped me.
No, of course not.
Really?
Of course.
I'd die if I said that.
I told him that you were messing around. What?
What's wrong with that? I've already had people from work and the manager stop me, but I should've told you. As a refuge.
We'll just say "Mr. Anashi".
Okay, fine.
Did you get to the takoyaki place?
All right.
We're here?
Thank you very much.
Okay.
Subscribe to that channel.